The Tufts Historical Review UP270
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
The Tufts Historical Review
2008 -- 2018
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Department of History
UP270
0.3 Linear Feet 1 document box
This collection contains issues of The Tufts Historical Review.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically in one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of The Tufts Historical Review.
Biographical / Historical
The Tufts Historical Review is the official publication of the Department of History at Tufts and the Tufts Historical Society, which was founded in 2007. It is an academic publication of the College of Arts & Sciences at Tufts University that is led primarily by Tufts undergraduate students.
Student Activities -- Student Publishing; Teaching and learning
- The Tufts Historical Review, 2008 -- 2018; UP270.000001
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - The Tufts Historical Review, 2008; UP270.000011 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Volume, issue
    1, 1
  - The Tufts Historical Review, 2009; UP270.000012 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    2, 1
  - The Tufts Historical Review, Spring 2010; UP270.000002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    3, 1
  - The Tufts Historical Review, Spring 2011; UP270.000003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    4, 1
  - The Tufts Historical Review, Spring 2012; UP270.000004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    5, 1
  - The Tufts Historical Review, Spring 2013; UP270.000005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    6, 1
  - The Tufts Historical Review, Spring 2014; UP270.000006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    7, 1
  - The Tufts Historical Review, 2015; UP270.000007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    8, 1
  - The Tufts Historical Review, 2016; UP270.000008 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    9, 1
  - The Tufts Historical Review, 2017; UP270.000009 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    10, 1
  - The Tufts Historical Review, 2018; UP270.000010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    11, 1
  - The Tufts Historical Review, 2019; UP270.000013 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Volume, number
    12, 1
  - The Tufts Historical Review, 2020; UP270.000014 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    13, 1
  - The Tufts Historical Review, 2021; UP270.000015 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    14, 1